[NEUTRAL]😐 Mr. Do not build a room, Mr. Do.
[NEUTRAL]😐 Need a charge.
[EPIC]⚡ We're actually going to do that too.
[EPIC]⚡ on.
[EPIC]⚡ That is just for the night, it's done.
[EPIC]⚡ information.
[EPIC]⚡ here.
[EPIC]⚡ there until it's dark.
[EPIC]⚡ sign.
[EPIC]⚡ down.
[EPIC]⚡ fast.
[EPIC]⚡ We don't let's sign this ring that's happening.
[EPIC]⚡ Why would we go to the middle of a-
[EPIC]⚡ where for who knows how long? Why?
[EPIC]⚡ wine.
[EPIC]⚡ Thank you.
[EPIC]⚡ ever happened in the history of the world. You're the great improviser, but this... you can't do it in your head. We're saying there's a chance that when we push that button, we destroy the world. Chances are near zero.
[EPIC]⚡ Here we go.
[EPIC]⚡ Zero.
[EPIC]⚡ .
[EPIC]⚡ This is a matter of life and death. I can't form this breath. World War II would be over. Our boys would come home. This happening isn't it? World? Well remember this day. Over here, will ensure a peace mankind has never seen. And if somebody visits a bigger wall.
[CALM]😌 and the power to destroy themselves.
[EPIC]⚡ 8... 7... 6... 5... 4...
[EPIC]⚡ Truman needs to know what's next. What's next? One.